plated.com 2019-09-04

# Privacy Policy | Plated

## Plated Online Privacy Policy

 **(Last Updated: July 17, 2017)**

Thank you for accessing the Plated Online Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”). This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information DineInFresh, Inc. d/b/a Plated (“Plated,” “we,” “our,” or “us”) may collect, how we may use this information, and when (under certain circumstances) we may disclose this information. This Privacy Policy also details the steps we take to secure your personal information.

You agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy in their entirety when you:

  * access or use the Plated.com Website or Plated Mobile Applications (collectively, the “Site”);
  * sign up to receive the Plated® food delivery service, which includes processing and delivery of orders (the “Plated Service”);
  * access links to Plated’s social media pages/accounts on third party social media websites, such as Facebook®, Instagram®, Pinterest®, Twitter®, Snapchat®, and YouTube® (collectively, “Social Media Pages”);
  * enter one of the sweepstakes, contests, and/or promotions offered by Plated® from time to time (“Promotions”); and/or
  * utilize the Site’s many interactive features designed to facilitate interaction between the end-user, Plated® and other Site users including, but not limited to, blogs and associated comment sections located in designated areas of the Site (collectively, the “Interactive Services” and together with the Site, Plated Service, Social Media Pages and Promotions, the “Plated Offerings”).

### IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY IN THEIR ENTIRETY, YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE PLATED OFFERINGS.

Facebook® is a registered trademark of Facebook, Inc. (“Facebook”). LinkedIn® is a registered trademark of LinkedIn Corporation (“LinkedIn”). Pinterest® is a registered trademark of Pinterest, Inc. (“Pinterest”). Twitter® is a registered trademark of Twitter, Inc. (“Twitter”). YouTube® is a registered trademark of Google, Inc. (“Google”).

also visit the Plated Terms and Conditions (“Terms and Conditions”) that explain other terms governing the use of our Site and associated Plated Offerings. Capitalized terms used but not defined herein shall have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms and Conditions.

### CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting an updated Privacy Policy at the Site. The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You should refer to this Privacy Policy on an ongoing basis so you understand our current Privacy Policy. Your continued use of Plated Offerings constitutes your: (a) acknowledgement of the Privacy Policy currently in effect; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the Privacy Policy.

### THIRD PARTY SITES

We are not responsible for the content on, or privacy practices of, any websites or services not owned or affiliated with Plated to which this Site links to or that links to this Site. Please be advised that Plated® is not in any way affiliated with Facebook, Google, LinkedIn, Pinterest or Twitter, and the Plated Offerings are not endorsed, administered or sponsored by any of those parties.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

 **We may collect several types of information from you directly and as described elsewhere in this policy, including information:**

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, username and password, shipping and billing information, e-mail address, telephone number, and/or credit card number (including security code and expiration date) (collectively, “Personally Identifying Information” or “PII”);
  * that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as your hobbies, personal interests, household income range, number of children, gender, demographic information, and product and service preferences; and/or
  * about others, such as the names and e-mail addresses of gift recipients or family and friends whom you have referred to the Site.

 **We may use the information we collect from you or receive about you, individually or combined:**

  * For registration and billing purposes;
  * To provide, maintain, and improve the Site and our products and services;
  * To respond to your questions and fulfill your orders and requests;
  * To verify entry into a Promotion and ship any prizes won in connection an applicable Promotion;
  * To personalize our services and offerings to you;
  * To communicate with you about your orders, our products, and the Site;
  * To manage your account and send you account related information;
  * To send you promotional messages and for targeted advertising purposes; and
  * For internal data modeling and marketing purposes.

 **We may collect information about you from other sources, as follows:**

  * If you access or log in to a Plated Offering through a social media website or other non-Plated service, or connect to a social media website or other non-Plated service through a Plated Offering, we may collect your user ID and/or user name associated with a third party social media service, any information or content you have permitted the social media service to share with us, such as your profile picture, email address or friends lists, and any information you have made public in connection with that social media service. When you engage in such activity, you are authorizing Plated to collect, store, and use such information and content in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
  * Plated may work with one or more data-modeling and/or data–append services which allow Plated to learn more about you from other sources, based on the information you have permitted Plated to gather directly (including your email address).
  * We may collect information about you from other third parties, such as our business partners.
  * We may combine the information we obtain from other sources with information we collect from you directly and use it for various purposes, such as to tailor advertising and content to you and send you offers that may be of interest.

 **We, our service providers (including advertising and analytics providers), and third parties may automatically collect several types of information about you including information:**

  * as you navigate through the Site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, operating system, browser type, referring URLs, access times, pages viewed, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies, such as information about your browsing and purchasing behavior.
  * about your mobile device.

This information is used to analyze trends, administer the Site and Plated Offerings, associated browsers and devices together, and deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests.

 **The technologies we, our service providers, and third parties may use for this automatic data collection may include:**

  *  **Cookies.** A cookie is a small removable data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer which often includes a unique identifier. Cookies are used to provide customers with tighter security, customized content, and tracking of orders and shopping cart items. Session cookies expire at the end of a particular visit to our Site, while persistent cookies (also called stored cookies) remain active until you disable them through your browser settings, or until a pre-set expiration date
  *  **Web Beacons.** Pages of our Site and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit us, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

You may disable or refuse to accept cookies through the appropriate browser settings, however if you select this setting you may not be able to use all features of our Site. In addition, disabling cookies may cancel opt-outs that rely on cookies, such as web analytics or targeted advertising opt-outs.

### INTEREST-BASED ADVERTISING

Plated may work with third parties who use cookies, tags, and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Site and other websites and apps on this browser or device and other browsers or devices associated with it to serve online ads likely to be of interest to you on your various devices and browsers, including ads for Plated products and services. This type of advertising is called interest-based advertising.

To learn more about interest-based advertising or to opt-out of having your web browsing information used for interest based advertising by companies that participate in the Network Advertising (“NAI:) or Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”), visit the websites operated by the NAI[<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>] and the DAA[<http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>]. Note, however, that not all service providers participate in the NAI and DAA. In addition, if you opt-out, you may still see online advertising from us and third parties, but the ads may be less relevant to you. If you delete or block cookies, buy or use a different device, access the Site from a different device, login under a different name, or change web browsers, you will need to opt-out again. Some web browsers may transmit “do not track” signals. At this time we do not take steps to respond to such signals.

### CUSTOMIZED AD CAMPAIGNS

Plated may work with third party service providers who use cookies and other technologies to (i) collect information about you automatically (such as your e-mail address) when you provide such information through the Site or when you access your Plated account, and (ii) collect additional information about your use of the Site and other websites. These service providers may combine the information collected with information they obtain from other sources and use the combined information to provide you with more relevant direct mail advertising on our behalf.

We may also work with third party social media sites, such as Facebook, to serve Plated ads to you as part of a customized social media campaign.

#### SHARING OF YOUR INFORMATION

### A.

We may share aggregated or de-identified information regarding our customers with partners, advertisers, or other third parties. This data will not identify you personally.

### B.

We may share information with companies that provide support services to us (such as a printer, mailing house, fulfillment company, delivery company, or web host) or that help us market our products and services. These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions. These companies are not authorized to use any personal information we share with them for any other purpose.

### C.

We (including, for all purposes hereof, any third parties that provide support services to Plated in connection with the Plated Offerings) will use the PII you provided to us to process, validate, confirm, verify, deliver and track your purchases (including by processing payment card transactions, arranging shipping and handling returns and refunds, and contacting you about your orders, including by telephone and/or the email address that you provide to Plated to communicate with).

### D.

As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a company sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, or similar event, the personal information and other information you provide to us or that we have gathered about you may be part of the transferred assets.

### E.

We may be required to disclose such information in response to subpoenas, court orders, requests from law-enforcement officials, or if we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law. If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect against and prevent fraud, unauthorized transactions, claims and other liabilities, and manage risk exposure of Plated, our customers or others, we may disclose your information as required. This includes identifying potential hackers and other unauthorized users to your account.

### F.

We may share your email address, other information you voluntarily provide to us, such as your hobbies, personal interests, household income range, number of children, gender, demographic information, and product and service preferences, and other information we may collect, including PII, with third-party partners for our, theirs and their customers’ marketing, analytics, content personalization, and other activities. We and our partners may combine such data with other data for these purposes.

### PROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION

We make commercially reasonable efforts to help keep your information secure and help protect your information from loss, theft, misuse, alternation, and unauthorized access or disclosure.

To further protect yourself, you should safeguard your Plated account username and password and not share that information with anyone. You should also sign off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit to our Site. Please note that we will never ask for your Plated account username or password via email.

### OPT OUT POLICY AND PROCEDURES

 **You may opt out of the following:**

  *  **Receipt of marketing, promotional, and non-transactional email communications from Plated.** Click the “unsubscribe” link located at the bottom of any Plated account.
    *  **Please note: You cannot opt-out of transactional email communications related to your account.** We may continue to contact you for the purposes of communicating information relating to your request for Plated Offerings, your participation in a Promotion and to respond to inquiries made by you, as applicable, even if you have elected to opt-out of certain communications as provided above.

To opt-out of all communications from Plated you must cease utilizing the Plated Offerings, and other services related to the Plated Offerings.

### DATA TRANSFERS

You agree that your information will be transferred to and processed by Plated in the United States.

### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

We do not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If we become aware that we have collected personally identifiable information from a user of the Site who is under the age of thirteen, we will remove that child’s personal information from our files.

### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

If you are a California resident, you have a right to request, once per year, that we provide to you (i) a list of the categories of personal information about you that Plated has disclosed to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes during the calendar year preceding your request, (ii) the names and addresses of such third parties, and (iii) if the nature of the third parties’ business cannot reasonably be determined from their names, examples of the products or services marketed, if known to Plated, sufficient to give you a reasonable indication of the nature of the third parties’ business. To submit your request, please email help@plated.com, with the subject line “California Privacy” and your request in the body of your email.

### ACCESSING AND MODIFYING INFORMATION

You may update, modify, and/or correct your information by logging into your Plated account or by email. Note, however, that Plated will continue to retain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes.

### QUESTIONS AND FEEDBACK

We welcome your questions, comments and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue at help@plated.com. You also may write to us at:

Plated  
Attn: Legal Department  
111 W19th Street, 3rd Floor  
New York, New York 10011
